{
    "subject": "Gloria_Stuart",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Arthur_Sheekman",
    "human_readable": "Gloria Stuart was married to Arthur Sheekman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9821562170982361,
            "question": "Were Gloria Stuart and Arthur Sheekman married for a long time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9371211528778076,
            "question": "Who was Gloria Stuart married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9255690574645996,
            "question": "To whom was Arthur Sheekman married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8605381846427917,
            "question": "What do you know about the relationship between Gloria Stuart and Arthur Sheekman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.846477746963501,
            "question": "Was Gloria Stuart ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6853433847427368,
            "question": "Who is Arthur Sheekman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6756536960601807,
            "question": "What is the name of Gloria Stuart's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42941322922706604,
            "question": "Who were some notable people in Gloria Stuart's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3121972978115082,
            "question": "Was Arthur Sheekman involved in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2262766808271408,
            "question": "What can you tell about Gloria Stuart's personal life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gloria Stuart was married to Arthur Sheekman.",
            "html": "yago_4692_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Arthur Sheekman involved in the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "yago_4692_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some notable people in Gloria Stuart's life?",
            "html": "yago_4692_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Gloria Stuart's husband?",
            "html": "yago_4692_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4692_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The first document mentions that \"Gloria Stuart and Arthur Sheekman were married for 43 years\" which implies they were married.\n* The second document confirms that \"Arthur Sheekman was previously married to Gloria Stuart (1934 - 1978)\".\n* The third document also mentions that \"Stuart then went on to marry screenwriter Arthur Sheekman in 1934 who died in 1978\".\n* The fourth and fifth documents further confirm the marriage between Gloria Stuart and Arthur Sheekman.\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that Gloria Stuart was indeed married to Arthur Sheekman, specifying the marriage date (28 July 1934) and duration (until his death in 1978)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}